<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.github.ddv1982.qa-scribe</id>
  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <name>QA Scribe</name>
  <summary>Local-first desktop testing notepad</summary>
  <description>
    <p>QA Scribe helps testers turn exploratory testing sessions, evidence, findings, and notes into structured testware while keeping project data local.</p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">qa-scribe.desktop</launchable>
  <provides>
    <binary>qa-scribe</binary>
  </provides>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/ddv1982/qa-scribe</url>
  <categories>
    <category>Office</category>
    <category>ProjectManagement</category>
  </categories>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.7.11" date="2026-07-12" />
    <release version="0.7.10" date="2026-07-09">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Give debug Tauri builds their own app identity and visible dev window title.</li>
          <li>Make Rust builds re-embed changed prebuilt frontend assets instead of shipping stale UI files.</li>
          <li>Bundle the Inter Variable italic face and tighten closed-stdout streaming regression coverage.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.9" date="2026-07-08">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix rich editor toolbar buttons so mouse clicks preserve selected text before TipTap formatting commands run.</li>
          <li>Keep block-style and link editing controls usable while safely restoring editor selections after native controls receive focus.</li>
          <li>Add regression coverage for toolbar focus preservation, link workflows, and stale selection cancellation paths.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.8" date="2026-07-08">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Copy notes for Jira with a rich HTML clipboard flavor alongside the plain Markdown fallback.</li>
          <li>Replace the custom editor HTML sanitizer core with DOMPurify under the same allowlist and URL policy.</li>
          <li>Serialize Jira clipboard Markdown via TipTap's static renderer with pinned, unchanged output.</li>
          <li>Add characterization and golden tests for sanitizer and clipboard behavior.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.7" date="2026-07-08">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Add Rust dependency auditing to the broad local release gate and release workflow documentation.</li>
          <li>Prevent provider-process cleanup hangs and reject oversized clipboard image transforms before allocation.</li>
          <li>Enforce Session-managed attachment paths and clarify rich-record body format reset behavior.</li>
          <li>Add keyboard focus navigation for note and AI model listboxes.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.6" date="2026-07-08">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Preserve dirty Draft and Finding edits and materialize inline images through managed attachments before persistence.</li>
          <li>Validate generated managed image references and cap custom Testware instructions before AI prompts and metadata are built.</li>
          <li>Tighten release validation, Tauri command permissions, Rust dependency auditing, and Windows provider-process cleanup.</li>
          <li>Improve Settings accessibility, CSS token checks, and production frontend bundle splitting.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.5" date="2026-07-08">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Preserve pending Note, Draft, and Finding edits across Session switches and window close.</li>
          <li>Sanitize generated rich HTML and persist generated outputs with AI Run completion atomically.</li>
          <li>Bound concurrent AI jobs and clean up provider probe child process groups.</li>
          <li>Strengthen release validation ordering and rich editor accessibility semantics.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.4" date="2026-07-08">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Preserve pending Note, Draft, and Finding edits across Session switches and window close.</li>
          <li>Sanitize generated rich HTML and persist generated outputs with AI Run completion atomically.</li>
          <li>Bound concurrent AI jobs and clean up provider probe child process groups.</li>
          <li>Strengthen release validation and rich editor accessibility semantics.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.3" date="2026-07-07">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Keep startup bounded by skipping full current-schema foreign-key scans while still validating migrations.</li>
          <li>Boot from a bounded recent Session list and minimal active Note state.</li>
          <li>Load Draft and Finding bodies lazily when their views or creation flows need them.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.2" date="2026-07-06">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Enforce safe attachment relative paths for all core callers.</li>
          <li>Keep note title autosave from applying stale saves.</li>
          <li>Allow Finding kind and metadata edits after creation.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.7.1" date="2026-07-06" />
    <release version="0.7.0" date="2026-07-06" />
    <release version="0.6.3" date="2026-07-05" />
    <release version="0.6.2" date="2026-07-05" />
    <release version="0.6.1" date="2026-07-03" />
    <release version="0.6.0" date="2026-07-03" />
    <release version="0.5.0" date="2026-07-03" />
    <release version="0.4.24" date="2026-07-02" />
    <release version="0.4.23" date="2026-07-02" />
    <release version="0.4.22" date="2026-06-25" />
    <release version="0.4.21" date="2026-06-25" />
    <release version="0.4.20" date="2026-06-25" />
    <release version="0.4.19" date="2026-06-24" />
  </releases>
</component>
